Now I am constantly plotting figures, so it's good to write down what I find out.

- There seems to be a delay between the two datasets: is this a known issue?

- The correlation length in methane emissions really smooths out CH4 emissions
without significantly reducing the quality of the fit. Is it realistic to
have these really smooth emissions.

- When I vary the fmcf errors, of course the emissions deviations in MCF become less
large. But foh and fch4 seem to start to correlate then. So for now my best
guess would be that the MCF emission errors are just that large.

- ​The chi-squared test (J_post = n/2) passes best if I put the prior error at 
50% of what I called normal. This kind of smoothes out the relative deviations,
which is probably realistic - or at least as much as I can say based on the data -
anyway.

- Should I have higher prior CH4 emissions? What is a good source for a methane budget?
515 Tg/yr in Bousquet (2011)

- There is a delay between the two datasets. Holmes et al. (2013) report a phasing
difference of 3 months, but mine seems around one year.
2008-2009 data interruption?

TODO:

- Look at AGAGE and NOAA data and find out where the delay comes from.